Rakhman Abdurakhmanov

About Me

I am a hardworking and responsible programmer with two years of commercial development experience in frontend. I have experience with React and TypeScript. I have a good understanding of layout design and excellent knowledge of JavaScript. But I can learn any technology in a reasonable amount of time if needed.

Education

Petrozavodsk State UniversityPetrozavodsk, Russian FederationM.S. in Mathematics09/2018 - 06/2020Petrozavodsk State UniversityPetrozavodsk, Russian FederationB.Eng. in Electronics09/2014 - 06/2018

Experience

Front-end Developer

inter://so

02/2022 - 09/2022

• At inter://so, I worked as the main front-end developer on their startup project. I started the project from scratch and was responsible for the project architecture and technologies used.

Front-end Developer

axmit

06/2019 - 10/2020

• In axmit I worked on many outsourcing projects, such as Zelos and Activatica. I was mostly involved in project support. I mean fixing bugs and adding new features.

Skills

Programming Languages:

- Js JavaScript / TS TypeScript
- **5** HTML
- ∘ **3** CSS

Libraries and Frameworks:

- o 🌼 React
- ∘ **V** Vue

Tools:

- o 🔁 Bash
- Docker
- **♦** Git

Languages:

- o English (B1)
- Russian (Native)